A Guide to the Papers of The Colson-Hill Family
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Family Correspondence, Telegrams,and Postcards-1845,1866-1980 1845,1866-1980
  - Family Correspondence
    - Family Correspondence 1915 (Box-folder 5:10)
    - Family Correspondence 1916 (Box-folder 5:11)
    - Family Correspondence 1917 (Box-folder 5:12)
    - Family Correspondence 1918 (Box-folder 5:13)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-May 1919 (Box-folder 6:1)
    - Family Correspondence Jun-Dec 1919 (Box-folder 6:2)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jul 1920 (Box-folder 6:3)
    - Family Correspondence Aug-Dec 1920 (Box-folder 6:4)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Apr 1921 (Box-folder 6:5)
    - Family Correspondence May-Oct 1921 (Box-folder 6:6)
    - Family Correspondence Nov-Dec 1921 (Box-folder 6:7)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Apr 1922 (Box-folder 6:8)
    - Family Correspondence May-Dec 1922 (Box-folder 6:9)
    - Family Correspondence 1923 (Box-folder 6:10)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Aug 1924 (Box-folder 6:11)
    - Family Correspondence Sept-Dec 1924 (Box-folder 6:12)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Apr 1925 (Box-folder 7:1)
    - Family Correspondence Aug 1925 (Box-folder 7:2)
    - Family Correspondence Sept 1925 (Box-folder 7:3)
    - Family Correspondence Oct-Dec 1925 (Box-folder 7:4)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Mar 1926 (Box-folder 7:5)
    - Family Correspondence Apr-Jul 1926 (Box-folder 7:6)
    - Family Correspondence Aug-Dec 1926 (Box-folder 7:7)
    - Family Correspondence-Dartmouth 1909-1926 (Box-folder 7:8)
    - Family Correspondence- Death of William Nelson Colson 1926 (Box-folder 7:9)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-May 1927 (Box-folder 7:10)
    - Family Correspondence Jun-July 1927 (Box-folder 7:11)
    - Family Correspondence Aug-Oct 1927 (Box-folder 8:1)
    - Family Correspondence Nov 1927 (Box-folder 8:2)
    - Family Correspondence Dec 1927 (Box-folder 8:3)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Feb 1928 (Box-folder 8:4)
    - Family Correspondence Mar-Apr 1928 (Box-folder 8:5)
    - Family Correspondence May-Jun 1928 (Box-folder 8:6)
    - Family Correspondence Jul-Aug 1928 (Box-folder 8:7)
    - Family Correspondence Sept-Oct 1928 (Box-folder 8:8)
    - Family Correspondence Nov 1928 (Box-folder 8:9)
    - Family Correspondence Dec 1928 (Box-folder 8:10)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Feb 1929 (Box-folder 9:1)
    - Family Correspondence Mar-May 1929 (Box-folder 9:2)
    - Family Correspondence Jun-Sept 1929 (Box-folder 9:3)
    - Family Correspondence Oct-Dec 1929 (Box-folder 9:4)
    - Family Correspondence 1930 (Box-folder 9:5)
    - Family Correspondence 1931 (Box-folder 9:6)
    - Family Correspondence Jun-Dec 1932 (Box-folder 9:7)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jun 1933 (Box-folder 9:8)
    - Family Correspondence Jul-Dec 1933 (Box-folder 9:9)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Sept 1934 (Box-folder 9:10)
    - Family Correspondence Oct-Dec 1934 (Box-folder 9:11)
    - Family Correspondence Mar-Jul 1935 (Box-folder 10:1)
    - Family Correspondence Sept-Dec 1935 (Box-folder 10:2)
    - Family Correspondence 1936 (Box-folder 10:3)
    - Family Correspondence 1937 (Box-folder 10:4)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Mar 1938 (Box-folder 10:5)
    - Family Correspondence Jun-Dec 1938 (Box-folder 10:6)
    - Family Correspondence 1939 (Box-folder 10:7)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jun 1940 (Box-folder 10:8)
    - Family Correspondence Aug-Dec 1940 (Box-folder 10:9)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jul 1941 (Box-folder 10:10)
    - Family Correspondence Aug-Dec 1941 (Box-folder 10:11)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jun 1942 (Box-folder 10:12)
    - Family Correspondence (Box-folder 10:13)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-May 1943 (Box-folder 11:1)
    - Family Correspondence June-Dec 1943 (Box-folder 11:2)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Sept 1944 (Box-folder 11:3)
    - Family Correspondence Oct-Dec 1944 (Box-folder 11:4)
    - Family Correspondence 1945 (Box-folder 11:5)
    - Family Correspondence 1946 (Box-folder 11:6)
    - Family Correspondence 1947 (Box-folder 11:7)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jun 1948 (Box-folder 11:8)
    - Family Correspondence Jul-Dec 1948 (Box-folder 11:9)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-May 1949 (Box-folder 11:10)
    - Family Correspondence Jun-Dec 1949 (Box-folder 11:11)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Sept 1950 (Box-folder 11:12)
    - Family Correspondence Oct-Dec 1950 (Box-folder 11:13)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jul 1951 (Box-folder 12:1)
    - Family Correspondence Aug-Sept 1951 (Box-folder 12:2)
    - Family Correspondence Oct-Dec 1951 (Box-folder 12:3)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jun 1960 (Box-folder 13:1)
    - Family Correspondence Jul-Dec 1960 (Box-folder 13:2)
    - Family Correspondence 1961 (Box-folder 13:3)
    - Family Correspondence 1962 (Box-folder 13:4)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jul 1963 (Box-folder 13:5)
    - Family Correspondence Aug-Dec 1963 (Box-folder 13:6)
    - Family Correspondence 1964 (Box-folder 13:7)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jun 1965 (Box-folder 13:8)
    - Family Correspondence Jul-Dec 1965 (Box-folder 13:9)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jun 1966 (Box-folder 13:10)
    - Family Correspondence Jul-Dec 1966 (Box-folder 13:11)
    - Family Correspondence 1967 (Box-folder 13:12)
    - Family Correspondence 1968 (Box-folder 13:13)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jul 1969 (Box-folder 14:1)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jul 1970 (Box-folder 14:2)
    - Family Correspondence Aug-Dec 1970 (Box-folder 14:3)
    - Family Correspondence 1971 (Box-folder 14:4)
    - Family Correspondence 1972 (Box-folder 14:5)
    - Family Correspondence 1973 (Box-folder 14:6)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-May 1974 (Box-folder 14:7)
    - Family Correspondence Jun-Dec 1974 (Box-folder 14:8)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jun 1975 (Box-folder 14:9)
    - Family Correspondence Jul-Dec 1975 (Box-folder 14:10)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jun 1976 (Box-folder 14:11)
    - Family Correspondence Jul-Dec 1976 (Box-folder 14:12)
    - Family Correspondence Jan-Jun 1977 (Box-folder 15:1)
    - Family Correspondence Jul-Dec 1977 (Box-folder 15:2)
    - Family Correspondence 1978 (Box-folder 15:3)
    - Family Correspondence 1979 (Box-folder 15:4)
    - Family Correspondence 1980 (Box-folder 15:5)
    - Family Correspondence-James M. Colson Jr. (Box-folder 15:6)
    - Family Correspondence- Kate Colson (Box-folder 15:7)
    - Family Correspondence- Kate Colson (Box-folder 15:8)
    - Family Correspondence- John H. Hill (Box-folder 15:9)
    - Family Correspondence- Fannie Mead Colson (Box-folder 15:10)
    - Family Correspondence- James Maor Colson III (Box-folder 15:11)
    - Family Correspondence- Cortland Colson (Box-folder 15:12)
    - Family Correspondence- Cortland Colson (Box-folder 15:13)
    - Family Correspondence- Jimmy Colson (Box-folder 15:14)
    - Family Correspondence- Myra Colson (Box-folder 15:15)
    - Family Correspondence- Myra Colson (Box-folder 15:16)
    - Family Correspondence- William N. Colson (Box-folder 15:17)
    - Family Correspondence- Susie Basset (Box-folder 15:18)
    - Family Correspondence- Elsie Colson (Box-folder 15:19)
    - Family Correspondence- H. Colson Jackson (Box-folder 15:20)
    - Family Correspondence- Constance Lewis (Box-folder 15:21)
    - Family Correspondence- Alvin Winfield (Box-folder 15:22)
    - Family Correspondence- Naomi Winfield (Box-folder 15:23)
    - Family Correspondence- Ernestine Colson (Box-folder 15:24)
    - Family Correspondence- Sue (Hill) Colson (Box-folder 15:25)
    - Family Correspondence- Gertrude (Colson) Jackson (Box-folder 15:26)
    - Family Correspondence- Jeanne (Colson) Baker (Box-folder 15:27)
    - Family Correspondence- Hattie (Colson) Freeman (Box-folder 15:28)
    - Family Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson (Box-folder 15:29)
    - Family Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson (Box-folder 15:30)
    - Family Correspondence- Unknown (Box-folder 15:31)
  - William Nelson Colson 1907-1922
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1907-1909 (Box-folder 16:1)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1910 (Box-folder 16:2)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson Jan-Jun 1911 (Box-folder 16:3)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson Jul-Dec 1911 (Box-folder 16:4)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1912 (Box-folder 16:5)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1913 (Box-folder 16:6)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1914 (Box-folder 16:7)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1915 (Box-folder 16:8)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1916 (Box-folder 16:9)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson Jan-Jun 1917 (Box-folder 16:10)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson Jul-Dec 1917 (Box-folder 16:11)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson Mar-Apr 1918 (Box-folder 17:1)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson May-Aug 1918 (Box-folder 17:2)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson Sept-Dec 1918 (Box-folder 17:3)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1919 (Box-folder 17:4)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1920 (Box-folder 17:5)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1921 (Box-folder 17:6)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1922 (Box-folder 17:7)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1923 (Box-folder 17:8)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1925 (Box-folder 17:9)
    - Correspondence- William N. Colson 1926 (Box-folder 17:10)
    - Personal Correspondence- William Nelson Colson 1908-1914 (Box-folder 17:11)
    - Personal Correspondence- William Nelson Colson 1915-1916 (Box-folder 17:12)
    - Personal Correspondence- William Nelson Colson (Box-folder 17:13)
    - Wedding Announcement 1918 (Box-folder 17:14)
    - Death of William Nelson Colson (Box-folder 17:15)
    - William N. Colson Va Union Baseball Team 1912 (Box-folder 18:1)
    - William N. Colson-Printed (Box-folder 18:2)
    - William N. Colson - News Clippings (Box-folder 18:3)
    - William N. Colson- Printed (Box-folder 18:4)
    - William N. Colson-367th (Box-folder 18:5)
    - William N. Colson- Bills 1909 (Box-folder 18:6)
  - Colson Woody 1950-1967
    - Colson/Woody Correspondence 1950-1966 (Box-folder 18:7)
    - Colson/Woody Correspondence Jan-Jun 1967 (Box-folder 18:8)
    - Colson/Woody Correspondence Jul-Dec 1967 (Box-folder 18:9)
    - Colson/Woody Correspondence 1968-1971 (Box-folder 18:10)
    - Wills (Box-folder 18:11)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 18:12)
  - The John and Mary Colson Shore Papers 1844-1877
    - Reciepts and Bills 1844-1845 (Box-folder 19:1)
    - Reciepts and Bills 1846-1847 (Box-folder 19:2)
    - Reciepts and Bills 1848-1849 (Box-folder 19:3)
    - Reciepts and Bills 1850 (Box-folder 19:4)
    - Reciepts and Bills 1851-1852 (Box-folder 19:5)
    - Reciepts and Bills 1853 (Box-folder 19:6)
    - Reciepts and Bills 1854-1855 (Box-folder 19:7)
    - Reciepts and Bills 1856 (Box-folder 19:8)
    - Reciepts and Bills 1857 (Box-folder 19:9)
    - Reciepts and Bills 1858 (Box-folder 19:10)
    - Reciepts and Bills 1859 (Box-folder 19:11)
    - Reciepts and Bills 1860 (Box-folder 19:12)
    - Reciepts and Bills 1861-1868 (Box-folder 19:13)
    - Correspondence 1877 (Box-folder 19:14)
    - The Grand Mount Hebram Tab (Box-folder 19:15)
    - Reciepts and Bills (Box-folder 19:16)
    - Reciepts and Bills (Box-folder 19:17)
    - Reciepts and Bills (Box-folder 19:18)
  - The John and Susie Hill Harris Papers 1900,1924
    - Reciepts and Bills 1891 (Box-folder 19:19)
    - Correspondence 1900-1929 (Box-folder 19:20)
    - Photography (Box-folder 19:21)
    - Deed-Presbyterian Church 1892 (Box-folder 19:22)
  - Family Personal
    - Correspondence-Personal 1859-1867 (Box-folder 20:1)
    - Correspondence- Family Personal 1881 (Box-folder 20:2)
    - Correspondence- Family Personal-Employment 1877-1883 (Box-folder 20:3)
    - Correspondence- Family Personal 1882-1883 (Box-folder 20:4)
    - Correspondence- Family Personal 1884 (Box-folder 20:5)
    - Correspondence- Family Personal 1885 (Box-folder 20:6)
    - Correspondence- Family Personal 1888,90,95 (Box-folder 20:7)
    - Correspondence- Family Personal 1898-1908 (Box-folder 20:8)
    - Correspondence- Family Personal 1904-1909 (Box-folder 20:9)
    - Correspondence- Family Personal 1912-1928 (Box-folder 20:10)
    - Correspondence- Employment 1914 (Box-folder 20:11)
  - Family Business
    - The House of Roberts and Colson 1833-1836 (Box-folder 21:1)
    - The House of Roberts and Colson 1833-1836 (Box-folder 21:2)
    - Correspondence- Family Business 1902-1910 (Box-folder 21:3)
    - Business General 1912-1923 (Box-folder 21:4)
    - Correspondence- Family Business 1924-1926 (Box-folder 21:5)
    - Correspondence- Family Business 1927-1936 (Box-folder 21:6)
    - Correspondence- Family Business 1937-1938 (Box-folder 21:7)
    - Correspondence- Family Business 1940-1949 (Box-folder 21:8)
    - Correspondence- Family Business 1941 (Box-folder 21:9)
    - Correspondence- Family Business 1942-1944 (Box-folder 21:10)
    - Correspondence- Family Business (Property) 1946-1949 (Box-folder 21:11)
    - Correspondence- Family Business 1951-1959 (Box-folder 21:12)
    - Property- Perry St., Harding, and Byrne 1906-1928 (Box-folder 22:1)
    - Colson/Walker Correspondence 1909-1920 (Box-folder 22:2)
    - Colson/Walker Correspondence 1921-1925 (Box-folder 22:3)
    - Building on Sycamore Street 1916-1917 (Box-folder 22:4)
    - Drawing of building on Sycamore Street 1916-1917 (Box-folder 22:5)
    - Rental Correspondence Eyerton 1909-1914 (Box-folder 22:6)
    - House on Bolling 1922-1928 (Box-folder 22:7)
    - Property on Harrison Street 1933 (Box-folder 22:8)
  - Family Work (school)
    - Correspondence- John A. Dix 1907-1908 (Box-folder 23:1)
    - Correspondence- John A. Dix 1909 (Box-folder 23:2)
    - Correspondence- John A. Dix 1910-1911 (Box-folder 23:3)
    - National Association of Teachers (Dix) 1906-1909 (Box-folder 23:4)
    - Printed- John A. Dix- Catalogue 1902-1903 (Box-folder 23:5)
    - Student Roster (Box-folder 23:6)
    - Bills and Receipts- John A. Dix 1908-1912 (Box-folder 23:7)
    - Printed- John A. Dix 1906-1907 (Box-folder 23:8)
    - Dix Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 23:9)
    - Atkins- Kate Colson, S.G./Kate Colson (Box-folder 23:10)
- Edna Colson(Personal, Colson/Meredith, Education, Employment) 1905-1984
  - Personal Correspondence
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1905-1911 (Box-folder 24:1)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1912-1913 (Box-folder 24:2)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1914 (Box-folder 24:3)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1915 (Box-folder 24:4)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1916 (Box-folder 24:5)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1917 (Box-folder 24:6)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1918 (Box-folder 24:7)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1919 (Box-folder 24:8)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1920-1921 (Box-folder 24:9)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1922-1924 (Box-folder 24:10)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1925-1926 (Box-folder 24:11)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1927 (Box-folder 24:12)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1928 (Box-folder 24:13)
    - Mothers Death 1928-1929 (Box-folder 24:14)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1929 (Box-folder 24:15)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1930 (Box-folder 25:1)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson Jan-Mar 1931 (Box-folder 25:2)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson Apr-Dec 1931 (Box-folder 25:3)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1932 (Box-folder 25:4)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson Jan-Jun 1933 (Box-folder 25:5)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson Jul-Dec 1935 (Box-folder 25:6)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1934 (Box-folder 25:7)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1935 (Box-folder 25:8)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1936 (Box-folder 25:9)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1937 (Box-folder 25:10)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1938 (Box-folder 25:11)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1939 (Box-folder 25:12)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1940 (Box-folder 25:13)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1941 (Box-folder 26:1)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1941 (Box-folder 26:2)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1943 (Box-folder 26:3)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1944 (Box-folder 26:4)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1945 (Box-folder 26:5)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1946 (Box-folder 26:6)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1947 (Box-folder 26:7)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1948-1950 (Box-folder 26:8)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1951 (Box-folder 26:9)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1952 (Box-folder 26:10)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1953 (Box-folder 26:11)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1954 (Box-folder 26:12)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1955-1956 (Box-folder 26:13)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1957 (Box-folder 26:14)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1958-1960 (Box-folder 26:15)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1961-1962 (Box-folder 26:16)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1963-1965 (Box-folder 27:1)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1967-1969 (Box-folder 27:2)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1970-1975 (Box-folder 27:3)
    - Will Correspondence 1976 (Box-folder 27:4)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1976-1977 (Box-folder 27:5)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1978-1979 (Box-folder 27:6)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson 1980-1982 (Box-folder 27:7)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson (Box-folder 27:8)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson (Box-folder 27:9)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson (Box-folder 27:10)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson (Box-folder 27:11)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson (Box-folder 27:12)
    - Personal Correspondence- Edna Meade Colson (Box-folder 27:13)
    - E.M.C- Amos, Thyras (Box-folder 28:1)
    - E.M.C- Caliver, Ambrose (Box-folder 28:2)
    - E.M.C. Carter, Hermione (Box-folder 28:3)
    - E.M.C Colson, Cannon, Deborah, and Gertiude (Box-folder 28:4)
    - Colson Printed Florence, C.N. (Box-folder 28:5)
    - E.M.C Colson/Pawley 1974 (Box-folder 28:6)
    - E.M.C Calter, Vivian Flagy (Box-folder 28:7)
    - E.M.C Portrait of R.P. Daniel (Box-folder 28:8)
    - E.M.C. Gandy, C.B. 1947-1969 (Box-folder 28:9)
    - E.M.C Hancock, Gordan (Box-folder 28:10)
    - E.M.C Richardson, S.G. (Box-folder 28:11)
    - E.M.C A Study of A Professional Negro Women 1927 (Box-folder 28:12)
    - E.M.C. A Study of Professional Negro Women- Hancock/Colson 1926-1927 (Box-folder 28:13)
    - E.M.C A study of a Negro Women: Meeting, U of Pittsburgh 1927 (Box-folder 28:14)
    - E.M.C Council of Christian Association Race Relations (Box-folder 28:15)
    - E.M.C International Student Services Committee (Box-folder 28:16)
    - E.M.C Jackson Davis Business 1931 (Box-folder 28:17)
    - E.M.C Virginia Council on Human Relations (Box-folder 28:18)
    - E.M.C Virginia Society for Research (Box-folder 28:19)
    - E.M.C Columbia University (Box-folder 28:20)
    - E.M.C. Copplin teachers College (Box-folder 28:21)
    - E.M.C. Fisk 1914 (Box-folder 28:22)
    - E.M.C Fisk 1930 (Box-folder 28:23)
    - E.M.C. Fisk 1946 (Box-folder 28:24)
    - E.M.C Fisk- Personal 1950-1960 (Box-folder 28:25)
    - E.M.C. Fisk-Personal 1965 (Box-folder 28:26)
    - E.M.C Univ Mass Press 1969-1970 (Box-folder 28:27)
    - E.M.C Miners Teachers College 1937 (Box-folder 28:28)
    - E.M.C Winston-Salem State Teachers College 1928 (Box-folder 28:29)
    - E.M.C Opportunity 1936,1938 (Box-folder 28:30)
  - Correspondence- Colson/Meridith
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1916-1917 (Box-folder 29:1)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1918-1919 (Box-folder 29:2)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1926-1928 (Box-folder 29:3)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1929 (Box-folder 29:4)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1930 (Box-folder 29:5)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1936 (Box-folder 29:6)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1939 (Box-folder 29:7)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1946 (Box-folder 29:8)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1949 (Box-folder 29:9)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1950 (Box-folder 29:10)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1952 (Box-folder 29:11)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1954 (Box-folder 29:12)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1960-1961 (Box-folder 29:13)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence (Box-folder 29:14)
    - Home Improvements 1959-1960 (Box-folder 29:15)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1931-1937 (Box-folder 30:1)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1939-1941 (Box-folder 30:2)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1948-1950 (Box-folder 30:3)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1951-1955 (Box-folder 30:4)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1956-1961 (Box-folder 30:5)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1962-1968 (Box-folder 30:6)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1969-1972 (Box-folder 30:7)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1973 (Box-folder 30:8)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1974 (Box-folder 30:9)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1975 (Box-folder 30:10)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1976 (Box-folder 30:11)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence Jan-Jun 1977 (Box-folder 31:1)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence Jul-Dec 1977 (Box-folder 31:2)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1978 (Box-folder 31:3)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence Jan-May 1979 (Box-folder 31:4)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence Jun-Dec 1979 (Box-folder 31:5)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence Jan-May 1980 (Box-folder 31:6)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence Jun-Jul 1980 (Box-folder 31:7)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence Aug-Dec 1980 (Box-folder 31:8)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence 1981-1982 (Box-folder 31:9)
    - Colson/Merideth Correspondence (Box-folder 31:10)
    - Postcards Collected- European Tour (Box-folder 32:1)
    - Postcards Collected- European Tour (Box-folder 32:2)
    - Postcards Collected- European Tour (Box-folder 32:3)
    - Photos (Box-folder 32:4)
    - Photos (Box-folder 32:5)
    - European Trip Correspondence 1955 (Box-folder 32:6)
    - European Trip Diary (Box-folder 32:7)
    - European Trip Diary 1955
    - European Trip Printed (Box-folder 32:9)
    - European Trip Printed (Box-folder 32:10)
    - European Trip Printed (Box-folder 32:11)
    - European Tour Study Abroad- Temple (Box-folder 32:12)
  - Correspondence Education
    - Colson- Columbia Carney 1924-1930 (Box-folder 33:1)
    - Colson- Columbia Carney 1931-1941 (Box-folder 33:2)
    - Colson- Columbia Carney 1942-1964 (Box-folder 33:3)
    - Colson- Columbia Carney 1935 (Box-folder 33:4)
    - Colson- Columbia Carney Dist. 1936-1937 (Box-folder 33:5)
    - Colson- Columbia Carney Dist. 1939 (Box-folder 33:6)
    - Colson- Columbia Carney Dist. 1940 (Box-folder 33:7)
    - Colson- Columbia Carney Dist. 1941-1947 (Box-folder 33:8)
    - Colson (Education and Welfare of Negroes Recommendations) 1938 (Box-folder 33:9)
    - Columbia- Internal House (Box-folder 33:10)
    - Internal House Yearbook 1931 (Box-folder 33:11)
    - Colson- Dissertation Research Jan-Feb 1935 (Box-folder 34:1)
    - Colson- Dissertation Research Mar-Jun 1935 (Box-folder 34:2)